<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources> 
    <string-array name="translations_en">
         
        <item>Our Lord, let not our hearts deviate after You have guided us and grant us from Yourself mercy. Indeed, You are the Bestower.</item>
         
        <item>Our Lord, give us in this world [that which is] good and in the Hereafter [that which is] good and protect us from the punishment of the Fire.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, we have wronged ourselves, and if You do not forgive us and have mercy upon us, we will surely be among the losers.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, indeed we have heard a caller calling to faith, [saying], \'Believe in your Lord,\' and we have believed. Our Lord, so forgive us our sins and remove from us our misdeeds and cause us to die with the righteous.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, grant us from Yourself mercy and prepare for us from our affair right guidance.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, and grant us what You promised us through Your messengers and do not disgrace us on the Day of Resurrection. Indeed, You do not fail in [Your] promise.</item>
         
        <item>Our Lord, forgive us and our brothers who preceded us in faith and put not in our hearts [any] resentment toward those who have believed. Our Lord, indeed You are Kind and Merciful.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, pour upon us patience and plant firmly our feet and give us victory over the disbelieving people.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, do not impose blame upon us if we have forgotten or erred. Our Lord, and lay not upon us a burden like that which You laid upon those before us. Our Lord, and burden us not with that which we have no ability to bear. And pardon us; and forgive us; and have mercy upon us. You are our protector, so give us victory over the disbelieving people.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, do not place us with the wrongdoing people.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, decide between us and our people in truth, and You are the best of those who give decision.</item>

        <item>Our Lord, indeed we have believed, so forgive us our sins and protect us from the punishment of the Fire.</item>

        <item>Allah! I seek refuge in You from the knowledge which is not beneficial, and from a heart which does not fear (You), and from desire which is not satisfied, and from prayer which is not answered.</item>
         
        <item>O Allah, the Turner of the hearts, turn our hearts to Thine obedience.</item>

    </string-array>
     
</resources>
